

alefiya.murtuza@gmail.com

**+971 56 62 48 280** 

Dubai, UAE

## Alefiya Hozefa

**UX/UI** Designer





## **About me**

I am a usability designer, researcher and analyst with 3+ years of experience in the field of user experience (UX) and user-centered design (UCD). I help companies to excel and boost its identity, services and applications in the digital phase.

My expertise in design tools such as Sketch, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe illustrator and Figma enables me to create high-fidelity designs that effectively communicate design concepts to stakeholders.

## **Work Experience**

### Senior Product Designer

**Full Time** 

Creed & Bear Network





- · Created complete design system for "Aamia", with design tokens to improve flexibility.
- Designed the wallet, subscription and profile (3/5) modules of the "Aamia" project.
- Completed all user flows with responsive designs (mobile/tablet/web).

## Super Future Technology

**Full Time** 







- Headed the SF Chat IM project a chat application with crypto transfer feature.
- Created the Design System for SF Chat IM completed the whole mobile application.
- Worked on the mobile version of the SF crypto trading application with smart contracts.





**a** January 2023- May 2023

- Designed the Desktop application of Future Tank a crypto education platform.
- Created wireframes and moodboards for a crypto trading application for ROK market.
- Worked on their landing pages, favicons and feature graphics + 3D icons for user levels.

#### Associate UX Designer

**Full Time** 





april 2022 - December 2022

- · Part of the team working on the Artaah project a luggage delivery application.
- Designed various features for the Artaah mobile application.
- · Created user flows and journeys with detailed wireframes.

#### **Graphic Designer/Content Creator**

**Full Time** 

**■** Bravura Advertising LLC



april 2018 - August 2020

- Styled the company profile and branding for various organizations including logos.
- Planned, managed and created advertising and promotional materials for events.

## **Education**

## Foundation of UX Design

**Full Time** 

Coursera



October 202 - December 2022

#### BA (Hons) Media, Advertising and PR

Full Time

Middlesex University

Dubai

**July 2011 - June 2014** 

### Tools

Figma



Adobe Illustrator



**Adobe Photoshop** 



Sketch



Invision



# Professional Skills

**Design System** 

**Design Thinking** 

**UX Design Strategist** 

Prototyping

Wireframes and Moodboards

Micro Interactions

**User Research** 

**Usability Testing** 

**Problem Solving** 

**Information Architecture** 

## Lanuages

- English
- Urdu
- Hindi
- Gujarati